mosets.com 2016-11-23

# Mosets - Privacy Policy

Mosets Consulting ("Mosets", "we" and "us") respects the privacy of its users ("you") and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. 

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our service.  

By using our website or application (our "Service"), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our service, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience. 

#### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register through a website, a mobile application, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site. 

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our or othersâ€™ products, services, or content;
  * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our service in order to better serve you. 
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other service feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties.
  * To develop, display, and track content and advertising tailored to your interests on our Service and other sites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other sites;
  * To perform website or mobile application analytics.

#### How do we protect visitor information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. 

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. 

#### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

#### We use cookies to:

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site and service traffic and site interactions in order to offer better service experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

#### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our service. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our service and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. 

We do not specifically market to children under 13.
